<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.4">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2018-10-08T17:16:04+08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Kyle Escosia</title><subtitle></subtitle><author><name>Kyle Escosia</name></author><entry><title type="html">Introduction to Microsoft Power BI</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/introduction-to-power-bi" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Introduction to Microsoft Power BI" /><published>2018-10-08T00:00:00+08:00</published><updated>2018-10-08T00:00:00+08:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/MyFirstBlog</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/introduction-to-power-bi">&lt;style type=&quot;text/css&quot;&gt;
	.head-intro{
		font-size: 0.75rem;
	}
	.resp-container{
		position: relative;
	    overflow: hidden;
	    padding-top: 56.25%;
	}
	.resp-iframe {
	    position: absolute;
	    top: 0;
	    bottom: 10px;
	    left: 0;
	    width: 100%;
	    height: 100%;
	    border: 0;
	}
&lt;/style&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;[&lt;a href=&quot;/tags.html#powerBI&quot;&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;highligher-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;nobr&gt;powerBI&lt;/nobr&gt;&lt;/code&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/tags.html#beginner&quot;&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;highligher-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;nobr&gt;beginner&lt;/nobr&gt;&lt;/code&gt; &lt;/a&gt;]&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1&gt; Microsoft Power BI&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt; So you want to learn how to create dashboards in Power BI huh? Then this blog is for you! &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt; What is Microsoft Power BI?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;
		&lt;strong&gt;Microsoft Power BI &lt;/strong&gt;is a collection of software services, apps, and connectors that work together to turn your unrelated sources of data into coherent, visually immersive, and interactive insights. Whether your data is a simple Microsoft Excel workbook, or a collection of cloud-based and on-premises hybrid data warehouses, &lt;strong&gt;Power BI&lt;/strong&gt;  lets you easily connect to your data sources, visualize (or discover) what's important, and share that with anyone or everyone you want.
	&lt;/p&gt;
	&lt;div class=&quot;resp-container&quot;&gt;
		&lt;iframe class=&quot;resp-iframe&quot; src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/yKTSLffVGbk&quot; frameborder=&quot;0&quot; allow=&quot;autoplay; encrypted-media&quot; allowfullscreen=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;
	&lt;/div&gt;
	&lt;div&gt;
		In this blog, we'll be focusing more on &lt;strong&gt;Power BI Desktop&lt;/strong&gt;, as mentioned in the video, it is totally &lt;strong&gt;free!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt; 
		Here are the most common uses for Power BI Desktop:
		&lt;ul&gt;
			&lt;li&gt;Connect to data&lt;/li&gt;
			&lt;li&gt;Transform and clean that data, to create a data model&lt;/li&gt;
			&lt;li&gt;Create visuals, such as charts or graphs, that provide visual representations of the data&lt;/li&gt;
			&lt;li&gt;Create reports that are c ollections of visuals, on one or more report pages&lt;/li&gt;
			&lt;li&gt;Share reports with others using the &lt;strong&gt;Power BI service&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/li&gt;	
		&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;div&gt;
	&lt;h3&gt;Who is it for?&lt;/h3&gt;
	&lt;p&gt;
		Developers, Business Analysts, Executives are just examples of whom Power BI is for. 
	&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</content><author><name>kyle_escosia</name></author><category term="Power BI" /><category term="powerBI" /><category term="beginner" /><summary type="html">[powerBI beginner ] Microsoft Power BI So you want to learn how to create dashboards in Power BI huh? Then this blog is for you! What is Microsoft Power BI? Microsoft Power BI is a collection of software services, apps, and connectors that work together to turn your unrelated sources of data into coherent, visually immersive, and interactive insights. Whether your data is a simple Microsoft Excel workbook, or a collection of cloud-based and on-premises hybrid data warehouses, Power BI lets you easily connect to your data sources, visualize (or discover) what's important, and share that with anyone or everyone you want. In this blog, we'll be focusing more on Power BI Desktop, as mentioned in the video, it is totally free! Here are the most common uses for Power BI Desktop: Connect to data Transform and clean that data, to create a data model Create visuals, such as charts or graphs, that provide visual representations of the data Create reports that are c ollections of visuals, on one or more report pages Share reports with others using the Power BI service Who is it for? Developers, Business Analysts, Executives are just examples of whom Power BI is for.</summary></entry></feed>